(Sheldon:)You once had Leonard and me
get your television from your ex-boyfriend.
(Penny:)Apples and oranges here, Sheldon.
(Penny:)I'm telling you, that girl is a user,
skating through life on her looks...
...taking advantage of innocent men...
(Penny:)...getting auditions
for stupid network shows.
It just creams my corn.
- May I interject something here?
- Please.
(Sheldon:)You got the wrong mustard.
(Sheldon:)- Hi.
- Hi.
(Alicia:)Guess what? I got the part on CSI.
(Penny:)Oh, boy.
(Alicia:)Something wrong?
(Sheldon:)No, no, no.
You know what? Congratulations.
(Penny:)I think you'll make a great hooker.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
Hey, I gotta ask you something.
(Alicia:)How much do physicists make?
Um... Ah.
(Penny:)I don't know. I don't think a lot.
(Alicia:)Yeah, that's what I figured.